A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3 FA388
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Philippines, 1950-1994; 242; 85 Box(es)
  - Philippines - Social Sciences, 1971-1990; 242.S
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 2 of 9 (Box 57, Folder 626)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-02a pp. i-iii, 1-63
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 3 of 9 (Box 57, Folder 627)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-02a pp. 64-134
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 4 of 9 (Box 57, Folder 628)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-03a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 5 of 9 (Box 57, Folder 629)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-04a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 6 of 9 (Box 57, Folder 630)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-05a, -06b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 7 of 9 (Box 57, Folder 631)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-07a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 8 of 9 (Box 58, Folder 632)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-08a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1975; Folder 9 of 9 (Box 58, Folder 633)
      242 S / CAMS 1-75-08b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 1 of 19 (Box 58, Folder 634)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-01a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 2 of 19 (Box 58, Folder 635)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-02a, -03a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 3 of 19 (Box 58, Folder 636)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-04a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 4 of 19 (Box 58, Folder 637)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-05a, -05b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 5 of 19 (Box 58, Folder 638)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-06a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 6 of 19 (Box 58, Folder 639)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-06b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 7 of 19 (Box 58, Folder 640)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-07a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 8 of 19 (Box 59, Folder 641)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-07b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 9 of 19 (Box 59, Folder 642)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-07b (Appendix)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 10 of 19 (Box 59, Folder 643)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-08a pp. 1-196
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 11 of 19 (Box 59, Folder 644)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-08a pp. 197-394
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 12 of 19 (Box 59, Folder 645)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-09a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 13 of 19 (Box 59, Folder 646)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-09b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 14 of 19 (Box 60, Folder 647)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-10a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 15 of 19 (Box 60, Folder 648)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-10b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 16 of 19 (Box 60, Folder 649)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-11a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 17 of 19 (Box 60, Folder 650)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-12a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 18 of 19 (Box 60, Folder 651)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-12b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1976; Folder 19 of 19 (Box 60, Folder 652)
      242 S / CAMS 1-76-13a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 1 of 28 (Box 60, Folder 653)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-01a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 2 of 28 (Box 60, Folder 654)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-02a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 3 of 28 (Box 60, Folder 655)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-02b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 4 of 28 (Box 60, Folder 656)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-03a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 5 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 657)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-03b pp. i-v, 1-83
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 6 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 658)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-03b pp. A1-A146
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 7 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 659)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-04a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 8 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 660)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-05a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 9 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 661)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-05b, -06a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 10 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 662)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-06b
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 11 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 663)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-07a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 12 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 664)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-08a pp. 1-172
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 13 of 28 (Box 61, Folder 665)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-08a pp. 173-323
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 14 of 28 (Box 62, Folder 666)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-08b pp. 1-172
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 15 of 28 (Box 62, Folder 667)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-08b pp. 173-323
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 16 of 28 (Box 62, Folder 668)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-09a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 17 of 28 (Box 62, Folder 669)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-09b pp. 1-208
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 18 of 28 (Box 62, Folder 670)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-09b pp. 209-353
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 19 of 28 (Box 62, Folder 671)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-10a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 20 of 28 (Box 62, Folder 672)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-11a pp. 1-188
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 21 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 673)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-11a pp. 189-339
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 22 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 674)
      Labor Absorption, Intensity and Productivity in Taiwan, 1954-1971 242 S / CAMS 1-77-11a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 23 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 675)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-12a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 24 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 676)
      Productivity and Employment in a G. O. 47 Farm 242 S / CAMS 1-77-12a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 25 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 677)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-13a pp. 1-166
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 26 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 678)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-13a pp. 167-302
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 27 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 679)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-14a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1977; Folder 28 of 28 (Box 63, Folder 680)
      242 S / CAMS 1-77-15a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 1 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 681)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-01a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 2 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 682)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-02a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 3 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 683)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-03a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 4 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 684)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-04a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 5 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 685)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-05a, -06a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 6 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 686)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-07a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 7 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 687)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-08a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 8 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 688)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-09a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 9 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 689)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-10a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 10 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 690)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-11a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 11 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 691)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-12a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 12 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 692)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-14a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 13 of 15 (Box 64, Folder 693)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-15a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 14 of 15 (Box 65, Folder 694)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-16a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1978; Folder 15 of 15 (Box 65, Folder 695)
      242 S / CAMS 1-78-18a
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1979; Folder 1 of 6 (Box 65, Folder 696)
      242 S / CAMS 1-79-1
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1979; Folder 2 of 6 (Box 65, Folder 697)
      242 S / CAMS 1-79-2
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1979; Folder 3 of 6 (Box 65, Folder 698)
      242 S / CAMS [1-79-3]
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1979; Folder 4 of 6 (Box 65, Folder 699)
      242 S / CAMS 1-79-4
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1979; Folder 5 of 6 (Box 65, Folder 700)
      242 S / CAMS 1-79-5, -6
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1979; Folder 6 of 6 (Box 65, Folder 701)
      242 S / CAMS 1-79-7
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1980; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 702)
      242 S / CAMS 1-80-1, -2
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1980; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 703)
      242 S / CAMS 1-80-3
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1981; Folder 1 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 704)
      242 S / CAMS 1-81-3
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1981; Folder 2 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 705)
      242 S / CAMS 1-81-5, -6
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1981; Folder 3 of 5 (Box 66, Folder 706)
      242 S / CAMS 1-81-10
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1981; Folder 4 of 5 (Box 66, Folder 707)
      242 S / CAMS 1-81-11
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1981; Folder 5 of 5 (Box 66, Folder 708)
      242 S / CAMS 1-81-12
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 1 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 709)
      242 S / CAMS 1-82-1
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 2 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 710)
      242 S / CAMS 1-82-2
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 3 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 711)
      242 S / CAMS 1-82-3
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 4 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 712)
      242 S / CAMS 1-82-4
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 5 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 713)
      242 S / CAMS 1-82-5
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 6 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 714)
      242 S / CAMS 1-82-6, -7
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 7 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 715)
      242 S / CAMS 1-82-8
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 8 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 716)
      82-12
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 9 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 717)
      82-13
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1982; Folder 10 of 10 (Box 66, Folder 718)
      82-14
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 719)
      83-01
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 1 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 720)
      84-01
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 2 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 721)
      84-02
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 3 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 722)
      84-03, 84-04
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 4 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 723)
      84-05
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 5 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 724)
      84-06
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 6 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 725)
      84-07
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 7 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 726)
      84-08
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 8 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 727)
      84-09 pp. 1-102
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 9 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 728)
      84-09 pp. 103-261
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 10 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 729)
      84-10
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 11 of 15 (Box 67, Folder 730)
      84-11, 84-12
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 12 of 15 (Box 68, Folder 731)
      84-13
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 13 of 15 (Box 68, Folder 732)
      84-14 pp. 1-180
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 14 of 15 (Box 68, Folder 733)
      84-14 pp. 181-334
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Discussion Papers and Final Reports, 1984; Folder 15 of 15 (Box 68, Folder 734)
      84-15
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (I), 1973; Folder 1 of 8 (Box 68, Folder 735)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (II), November 1975; Folder 2 of 8 (Box 68, Folder 736)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (III), November 1975; Folder 3 of 8 (Box 68, Folder 737)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (IV), November 1975; Folder 4 of 8 (Box 68, Folder 738)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (V), February 1976; Folder 5 of 8 (Box 68, Folder 739)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (VI), July 1979; Folder 6 of 8 (Box 68, Folder 740)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (VII), July 1979; Folder 7 of 8 (Box 68, Folder 741)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Executive Council Meetings (VIII), January 1983; Folder 8 of 8 (Box 69, Folder 742)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Hauser-Oshima Policy Discussion, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 743)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Force Participation and Fertility Reports (I), August 1979; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 744)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Force Participation and Fertility Reports (II), August 1979; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 745)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Force Participation and Fertility Reports (III), August 1979; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 746)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Force Participation and Fertility Reports (IV), August 1979; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 747)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Supply Conference (I), June 1976; Folder 1 of 5 (Box 69, Folder 748)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Supply Conference (II), June 1976; Folder 2 of 5 (Box 69, Folder 749)
      242 S / CAMS 2 (1)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Supply Conference (III), June 1976; Folder 3 of 5 (Box 69, Folder 750)
      242 S / CAMS 2 (2)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Supply Conference (IV), June 1976; Folder 4 of 5 (Box 69, Folder 751)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Labor Supply Conference (V), June 1976; Folder 5 of 5 (Box 69, Folder 752)
      242 S / CAMS 2 (3)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Policy Manual (I), 1976; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 753)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Policy Manual (II), 1976; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 754)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Policy Manual (III), 1976; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 755)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Policy Manual (IV), 1976; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 69, Folder 756)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1974; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 70, Folder 757)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1974; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 70, Folder 758)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1974; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 70, Folder 759)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1974; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 70, Folder 760)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1975; Folder 1 of 7 (Box 70, Folder 761)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1975; Folder 2 of 7 (Box 70, Folder 762)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1975; Folder 3 of 7 (Box 70, Folder 763)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1975; Folder 4 of 7 (Box 70, Folder 764)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1975; Folder 5 of 7 (Box 70, Folder 765)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1975; Folder 6 of 7 (Box 70, Folder 766)
    - Council for Asian Manpower Studies - Supplementary Material - Proposals, 1975; Folder 7 of 7 (Box 71, Folder 767)